Six people had to move away from their home to another place after a fire broke out
in a building on Main Street, Saturday, officials said.
Firefighters responded to the three -story building shortly after 1 p.m.
for a reported structure fire, according to Norwalk Deputy Fire Chief Adam
Markowitz. Firefighters responded to the three -story building shortly after 1.m.
Markowitz. Firefighters responded to the three -story building shortly after 1 p.m.
for a reported structure fire, according to Norwalk Deputy Fire Chief Adam
Markowitz. Markowitz said crews encountered heavy smoke coming from the second floor
when they arrived.
A team of about 25 firefighters then spent about 25 minutes extinguishing the
flames. Markowitz said crews encountered heavy smoke coming from the second floor
when they arrived.
A team of about 25 firefighters then spent about 25 minutes extinguishing the
flames. Markowitz said crews encountered heavy smoke coming from the second floor
when they arrived.
A team of about 25 firefighters then spent about 25 minutes extinguishing the
flames. Officials described the structure as a mixed -use building that features
commercial businesses on the first floor and residential on the second and third
floors. Officials described the structure as a mixed -use building that features
floors. Town records list four apartments in the building.
Due to smoke and heat damage, the four apartments
Town records list four apartments in the building.
Due to smoke and heat damage,